the blue sky is now only a faint memory
its all distorted now;
the world is only covered in crimson
and lament of darkness
The beginning of this tragedy was
この悲劇ひげきの始はじまりは
nothing but a predetermined fate, it seems.
定さだめられた運命うんめいにほかならない
All that will remain is
残のこっているのは、砕くだけ散ちり、
the truth, shattered and scattered.
壊こわれた世界せかいという真実しんじつだけ
(entry: #5,888
the equation of this catastrophe
is only filled with demise
we are left with no more options
and now we only have so much time until the end of it all)
The world we once knew--
ぼくらが知しっていた世界せかい--
it's only crumbling to pieces now
崩くずれていくだけだ
this may be our last moment, our 「farewell」
under this black sky we call home...
この真っ黒まっくな空そらの下したで...
...so please, don't let go!
…放はなさないで!!